{"tossups": [{"question": "This political ideology is associated with a magazine edited by Norman Podhoretz. Commentary Magazine is the major organ of this political viewpoint, whose so-called \"godfather\" was Irving Kristol.Many of those who espouse this political viewpoint cite the writings of Leo Strauss (strose) as an influence. Many of the advisors to George W. Bush, including John Bolton and Paul Wolfowitz, are considered adherents to this view. FTP what political view is characterized by hawkish attitudes toward war and more aggressive US involvement in world affairs than paleo-conservatives?", "answer": "neo-conservatism [accept word forms; prompt on \"conservative\"] ", "category": "Social Science"}, {"question": "This process uses the RecA protein during the SOS response. This process is deficient in a hereditary variant of colon cancer called Lynch syndrome. One type of this process uses the MutS protein and another type uses AP endonuclease. Lindahl, Modrich, and Sancar won the 2015 Nobel Prize for their studies of this process. UV radiation and free radicals necessitate this process, which includes non-homologous end joining and nucleotide excision types. For 10 points, name this process in which cells fix the damage done to a certain double helical molecule.", "answer": "DNA repair [accept equivalents or specific types] ", "subcategory": "Science Biology", "category": "Science"}, {"question": "One literary character with this role acts as a detective in a series of linked stories like \"The Blue Cross\" and \"The Paradise of Thieves.\" Another character has tarnished his work in this profession by having an illegitimate daughter with Maria. That character with this profession is captured when he returns to see the gringo, who refuses to repent his sins before dying in the novel The Power and the Glory. Along with that character who has this profession modified by the adjective \"Whisky,\" another character with this profession terrifies Stephen Dedalus with his graphic depictions of the torments of hell in a sermon. FTP what religious profession do characters like Father Brown and Father Arnall share?", "answer": "Catholic priests", "subcategory": "Literature British", "category": "Literature"}, {"question": "In this country near the town of Mandera, 36 quarry workers were killed in an attack a week before 28 people, mostly teachers, were killed in a bus attack. This country's interior minister, Joseph Ole Lenku, was fired after those attacks. The town of Dadaab in this country is home to a camp with several hundred thousand refugees. More than 100 students at Garissa University were killed during an attack in this country, and more than 60 people were killed during a four-day siege at the Westgate shopping mall. Those attacks were carried out by the Somalia-based terrorist group al-Shabab. For 10 points, name this country whose president is Uhuru Kenyatta.", "answer": "Kenya", "category": "Current Events"}, {"question": "Two siblings of this race were tormented in Hades by a screech owl after trapping Ares in an urn for a year; those two, Otus and Ephialtes, also attempted to take Artemis and Hera as wives from Mount Olympus. Hoplodamus was one of these figures in Greek myth who, with his brothers, defended Rhea from Cronos. Heracles crushed one of these figures to death after lifting him from the Earth, from which he derived strength. FTP, Antaeus [an-TEE-uhs] was an example of what mythical race, of which Argos Panoptes is another example, all of whom were known for their great size?", "answer": "giants (do not accept \"Titans\"; they ain't)", "category": "Mythology"}, {"question": "n Seidl conducted the 1893 premiere of this work, which begins in 4/8 time. The beginning of the Scherzo third movement of this work was modeled on the beginning of the Scherzo second movement of Beethoven's ninth symphony. The composer of this E minor work traveled to Spillville, Iowa after its completion. Its second movement is marked Largo and contains an English horn solo that was adapted into \"Goin' Home,\" which has the form of an African-American spiritual. For 10 points, name this work by the Czech composer Antonin Dvorak. ", "answer": "Symphony No. 9, From the New World [accept either or New World Symphony] ", "subcategory": "Fine Arts Auditory", "category": "Fine Arts"}, {"question": "The 1904 Limerick Boycott targeted these people. One member of this group was displayed publically in a human-sized birdcage after he was accused of poisoning Karl Alexander I of Wurttemberg. Under the 1264 Statute of Kalisz, these people were given special courts and had funerals fully funded by the Polish nobility. These people in Russia were mostly forced to live in the Pale of Settlement in villages called \"shtetls\" where they were frequently attacked in pogroms. For 10 points, identify these members of a monotheistic faith persecuted by Christians in medieval Europe.", "answer": "Jews or Jewish Europeans", "subcategory": "History European", "category": "History"}, {"question": "A method used in this technique that uses 45, 90, and 135 degree decoupler pulses is known as distortionless enhancement by polarization transfer. In this technique, the relationship between a quantity symbolized J and dihedral angles is given by the Karplus equation. A commonly used solvent in this technique is deuterated chloroform. The compound TMS is used as a reference in this technique, which has proton and carbon-13 varieties. For 10 points, name this spectroscopic technique from organic chemistry that is used to determine the structure of molecules. ", "answer": "NMR spectroscopy [accept specific types; or nuclear magnetic resonance] ", "subcategory": "Science Chemistry", "category": "Science"}, {"question": "Chapter 87 of the Adi Parva declares that the refusal to use harsh words or wrong others when you have been wronged is a form of this practice. This practice in Judaism was known as Maasar Ani in Biblical Times, but in modern times is called tzedakah [suh-dah-KAH]. In Orthodox Christianity, one can avoid doing this by intercession or acts of mercy. This practice is known as Dana in Hinduism and is one of the pillars of Islam, Zakat. For 10 point, name this common religious practice usually referring to the giving of goods or money to the impoverished.", "answer": "Almsgiving (in Orlando be nice and prompt on \"tithing\")", "category": "Religion"}, {"question": "The first stage of this engagement began when a detachment of General Simon Fraser's regiment spotted the British near a farm owned by the loyalist John Freeman. The second phase of this engagement took place at Bemis Heights, where Daniel Morgan's riflemen were effective against British Grenadiers. This engagement was the culmination of General Burgoyne's invasion of the US, which was meant to capture all the Hudson River area to cut off New England from the rest of the colonies. This battle saw all of Burgoyne's troops captured by the forces of Horatio Gates. For 10 points, name this New York engagement considered the turning point of the American Revolution.", "answer": "Battle of Saratoga", "subcategory": "History American", "category": "History"}, {"question": "This literary genre is presented in fractured form in the William S. Burroughs novel The Place of Dead Roads. After the novel Suttree, Cormac McCarthy moved to a series of works featuring the hallmarks of this genre, starting with Blood Meridian. A series of 17 novels about Jubal Sackett was written by a master of this genre, Louis L'Amour. A famous work in this genre depicts Jane Withersteen's escape from a forced Mormon polygamous marriage with the help of Lassiter. FTP Riders of the Purple Sage by Zane Grey is an example of what American genre which often features gunfights and cowboys?", "answer": "Western (prompt on \"cowboy novel\" or \"oater\" if respondent over 80 years old)", "subcategory": "Literature American", "category": "Literature"}, {"question": "This quantity's namesake blending index is calculated when using the double-log Refutas equation. A device used to measure this quantity contains an outer cup and an inner bob, both of which are concentric cylinders. A term in Stokes's law is six pi times the product of velocity, radius, and this quantity. For stirred or shaken thixotropic materials, this quantity decreases, but for Newtonian fluids, it is constant. A dimensionless number named for Reynolds is defined by either the kinematic or dynamic types of this quantity. Molasses has a high value for this quantity, which is zero for superfluids. For 10 points, name this quantity that measures a fluid's resistance to flow.", "answer": "viscosity [accept specific types] ", "subcategory": "Science Physics", "category": "Science"}, {"question": "This nation fought an alliance of provinces in the Cisplatine War over a strip of land called the Banda Oriental. Members of the surviving branch of the Capetian Dynasty escaped to this nation after Napoleon occupied their nation in 1807. The Rio Branco Law freed the children of slaves in this country before the 1888 Golden Law abolished slavery entirely during the reign of Pedro II. Along with Argentina and Uruguay, this country defeated Paraguay in the War of the Triple Alliance. For 10 points, name this South American nation whose official language is Portuguese. ", "answer": "Brazil", "subcategory": "History World", "category": "History"}, {"question": "Mount Melbourne and Berlin are active volcanoes on this landmass. The American Highland is a region of this landmass featuring a large number of exposed rocky surfaces called nunataks. The Sentinel Range runs along this landmass and culminates near a peninsula called Graham Land. That peninsula's eastern coast is on the Weddell Sea. The highest point on this landmass is named for a Georgia senator. Vinson Massif is the tallest mountain on, FTP, what continent governed by seven countries and featuring the Ross Ice Shelf.", "answer": "Antarctica", "category": "Geography"}, {"question": "An author from this country wrote a short story in which two teenage girls write fake love letters to a housekeeper. Another author from this country wrote a work in which a boy accidentally hits a pregnant woman with a rock-filled snowball. The authors of \"Hateship, Friendship, Courtship, Loveship, Marriage\" and The Deptford Trilogy are both from this country, which is also the home of a female author who wrote a novel set in the Republic of Gilead in which Offred's only purpose is to produce offspring. For 10 points, name this country that is home to Alice Munro, Robertson Davies, and the author of The Handmaid's Tale, Margaret Atwood.", "answer": "Canada", "subcategory": "Literature World", "category": "Literature"}, {"question": "Donald Davidson presented one of these situations by suggesting the possibility of a \"Swampman\" created by lightning who shares all of Davidson's brain structure. Wittgenstein posited one in which individuals can only truly understand their own \"beetle in a box.\" John Searle invented an example in which a person translates Chinese script using an instruction set without really understanding the language. Daniel Dennett criticized that \"Chinese Room\" example as an \"intuition pump,\" suggesting it omits important implications of the problem. FTP what are these conceptual problems that posit a situation to exemplify questions in philosophy?", "answer": "thought experiments", "category": "Philosophy"}, {"question": "A memory management unit translates addresses described by this adjective to their physical locations. Paging can be used with memory described by this adjective. It's not \"guest\" or \"host,\" but a hypervisor supervises these types of machines, which can be used to emulate Windows on other devices. Java byte code is executed on a machine described by this adjective. A paradigm described by this adjective can be experienced using the HTC Vive device. For 10 points, name this word that describes a type of \"reality\" offered by the Oculus Rift. ", "answer": "virtual", "subcategory": "Science Computer Science", "category": "Science"}, {"question": "A work of art in this medium that depicts the Apocalypse and is located in Angers [ahn-ZHEY] was designed by Jean Bondol in the 14th century. William Knox D'Arcy commissioned a work of art in this medium that centers on the Holy Grail legend. Another work of art in this medium includes a dwarf named Turold who holds the reins of some horses. Seven works of art in this medium that hang in the Cloisters depict a hunt for a unicorn. Bishop Odo commissioned the most famous work in this medium, which depicts Halley's Comet and several events from the Norman invasion. For 10 points, identify this medium used for a 230 foot long work located in Bayeux.", "answer": "tapestry [or embroidery; or weaving; accept word forms] ", "subcategory": "Fine Arts Other", "category": "Fine Arts"}, {"question": "Christine Collins won a lawsuit against this city's police chief J.J. Jones in 1928 after Jones had her sent to an asylum when she challenged the assertion that a lying runaway was her abducted son. This city was home to a notorious \"Gun Squad,\" which was controlled by a later corrupt police chief James Davis. A truck driver named Reginald Denny was pulled from his truck in 1992 and beaten during a riot in this city that followed the police beating of a motorist who later at a press conference asked denizens of this city, \"Can't we all just get along?\" For 10 points, identify this city where the Rodney King riots occurred. ", "answer": "Los Angeles", "subcategory": "History American", "category": "History"}, {"question": "work with this title contains the idea of \"imaginary gardens with real toads in them.\" In a work entitled \"Introduction to\" this art form, some people want to tie a certain object to a chair and \"torture a confession out of it.\" Harriet Monroe founded a magazine with this title, and Wallace Stevens referred to it as \"the supreme fiction.\" A work by Marianne Moore with this title begins \"I, too, dislike it.\" Types of it include ghazals, tankas, and villanelles. For 10 points, name this type of literary work that has a metrical form and is often contrasted with prose.", "answer": "poetry [be generous and accept word forms, such as poems; or poetical works]", "subcategory": "Literature American", "category": "Literature"}], "bonuses": [{"leadin": "That a golden turtle called Kim Qui gave a sword to a 15th-century ruler is a folk myth from this country. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Vietnam", "Cao Dai", "Mahayana Buddhism"], "parts": ["Though officially atheist according to its communist government, what country has 6.2 million Catholics due to lingering effects of French colonial rule?", "Joan of Arc and Victor Hugo are saints in this syncretistic Vietnamese religion named for its supreme deity.", "By far the largest religion in Vietnam is this branch of Buddhism, a \u201cgreater vehicle\u201d that comprises many different Buddhist traditions."], "subcategory": "Religion East Asian", "category": "Religion"}, {"leadin": "The first book published by a woman in North America included a poem describing this event. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["house fire [accept equivalents]", "Anne Bradstreet", "Phillis Wheatley"], "parts": ["What home tragedy is chronicled in a poem from the collection The Tenth Muse Lately Sprung up in America which ends, \u201cMy hope and treasure lie above\u201d?", "The Tenth Muse was published without the knowledge of this female poet in America, who addressed another poem \u201cTo My Dear and Loving Husband\u201d?", "The first African-American woman to be published was this later author of \u201cTo His Excellency, George Washington.\u201d"], "subcategory": "Literature American", "category": "Literature"}, {"leadin": "This man developed three laws of spectroscopy, the first of which states that a hot dense gas produces a continuous spectrum. For 10 points each:", "answers_sanitized": ["Gustav Kirchhoff", "zero", "rubidium"], "parts": ["Name this physicist whose namesake junction and loop rules are used to analyze circuits.", "According to Kirchhoff's loop rule, the net change in potential around a closed loop of a circuit containing a twelve volt battery in series with a five ohm and one ohm resistor is this value.", "Kirchhoff, along with Robert Bunsen, discovered cesium and this other chemical element. Cornell and Wieman produced the first Bose-Einstein condensate using atoms of this element."], "subcategory": "Science Physics", "category": "Science"}, {"leadin": "One of these creatures is blind and led by a girl in an etching from the Vollard Suite. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Minotaur", "Pablo Picasso", "Marie-Therese Walter [accept either]"], "parts": ["Name this hybrid monster from Greek myth that was depicted in another work by the same artist reaching toward a girl with a candle, and is said to represent the artist\u2019s own sense of tenderness and rage.", "This artist's Vollard Suite includes fifteen etchings of Minotaurs. Some critics suggest the bull head in this artist\u2019s work Guernica is meant to represent a Minotaur.", "The little girls in the aforementioned etchings have the facial features of this Picasso mistress. Part of this woman's face comprises an erect penis in the painting The Dream."], "subcategory": "Fine Arts Visual", "category": "Fine Arts"}, {"leadin": "Between the February phase and this event, an April crisis occurred in which the Minister of Foreign Affairs sent a message to the Allies saying his country would stay in the war, but that stance was later reversed by the Treaty of Brest-Livotsk. For 10 points each:", "answers_sanitized": ["October Revolution (accept reasonable equivalent such as Bolshevik Revolution or Revolution of 1917, Do not accept October Crisis)", "Leon Trotsky", "White Army [or the Whites; or White Guard]"], "parts": ["Name this revolution that put Lenin and his supporters in power over the Provincial Government.", "This right hand man of Vladimir Lenin was exiled after the rise of Stalin, and he was killed in Mexico City with an icepick.", "This force fought the Bolsheviks after the October Revolution and was led by Alexander Kolchak."], "subcategory": "History European", "category": "History"}, {"leadin": "Pneumatophores [noo-MAT-uh-fohrs] are a type of these organs that are produced by plants growing in water, such as mangroves, in order to facilitate oxygen absorption. For 10 points each:", "answers_sanitized": ["roots", "Casparian strip", "fungi [or fungus]"], "parts": ["Name these plant structures that are usually located below ground and aid in anchorage.", "This structure in roots is located around the transverse and radial walls of endodermal cells. This structure is made up of material called suberin, which helps it serve as a diffusion barrier.", "A mycorrhiza [my-kuh-RY-zuh] is a symbiotic association between plant roots and these organisms, from which cephalosporins were first derived. Ascomycota is a phylum of these organisms whose members possess a complex called the Spitzenkorper."], "subcategory": "Science Biology", "category": "Science"}, {"leadin": "This literary character spent part of his life revising articles for The Ministry of Truth. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Winston Smith (accept either name)", "five", "Homage to Catalonia"], "parts": ["Name this character who finally denounces Julia after he\u2019s presented with the possibility of being eaten alive by rats in Room 101.", "Finally broken, Smith accepts the truth that 2+2 equals this number rather than four.", "Orwell described his time serving on the Aragon Front in this book about his service in the Spanish-American War."], "subcategory": "Literature British", "category": "Literature"}, {"leadin": "The Dasht-e Kavir, or Great Salt Desert, comprises the northern third of this nation. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Iran", "Persian Gulf", "Shatt al-Arab (or Stream of Arabs)"], "parts": ["The Zagros and Alburz Mountain ranges lie in the west and north of this country that contains the city of Isfahan.", "Iran\u2019s southwestern coast is on this body of water, crucially important to oil transportation.", "The Tigris and Euphrates rivers converge to flow into the Persian Gulf through this river named for the peoples who have lived around it for millennia."], "subcategory": "Geography World", "category": "Geography"}, {"leadin": "This man issued Special Field Order No. 15. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["William Tecumseh Sherman", "George McClellan", "Irvin McDowell"], "parts": ["Name this US general who led the March to the Sea from Atlanta to Savannah.", "This man ran against Lincoln for president in the 1864 election, but lost, partly due to Sherman\u2019s very successful March to the Sea.", "McClellan had earlier taken over the Army of the Potomac after this man fared poorly at the First Battle of Bull Run. He was also blamed for the Union\u2019s failures at the Second Battle of Bull Run."], "subcategory": "History American", "category": "History"}, {"leadin": "This goddess represents the dark aspect of Durga, the ur-feminine in Hindu myth. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Kali", "Shiva", "mouse"], "parts": ["What black-skinned goddess was worshipped by the Thuggee?", "Kali is often depicted with her foot on the chest of this member of the Trimurti, the husband of Parvati, sometimes given the epithet \u201cthe Destroyer.\u201d", "Shiva is the father of the elephant-headed Ganesha, who rides in a vehicle pulled by the deity Kroncha, who is one of these animals."], "subcategory": "Mythology Indian", "category": "Mythology"}, {"leadin": "This ballet was one of the \"Eight Model Operas\" created during the Cultural Revolution. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["The Red Detachment of Women [or Hongse niangzijun]", "China [or the People's Republic of China; or Zhongguo; or Zhonghua]", "September 11th attacks [or 9/11; accept obvious equivalents]"], "parts": ["Name this work in which Wu Qinghua joins the titular group and kills the evil Nan Batian.", "A performance of The Red Detachment of Women occurs in the John Adams opera Nixon in [this country]. That opera set in this nation includes characters such as Mao and Zhou Enlai.", "Another work by the composer John Adams is entitled On the Transmigration of Souls and was commissioned by the New York Philharmonic for the first anniversary of this event."], "subcategory": "Fine Arts Opera", "category": "Fine Arts"}, {"leadin": "This concept is sometimes considered the basis for the common American expectation that a woman\u2019s family should pay for a wedding. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["dowry", "India", "bride price or bride token"], "parts": ["What is this payment made by the family of a bride to her groom?", "Despite the 1961 Dowry Prohibition Act in this country, over 5,000 women were murdered by their husbands\u2019 families in 2014 in this country sadly known for such dowry killings.", "The opposite of dowry, this type of payment more common in agricultural societies compensates a family for the loss of a daughter\u2019s labor."], "subcategory": "Current Events Other", "category": "Current Events"}, {"leadin": "The main character on this show used a raspberry pi to access a climate control system. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Mr. Robot", "Emmy Rossum", "Comet"], "parts": ["Name this USA drama on which Rami Malek plays a computer hacker.", "Mr Robot was created by Sam Esmail, who is engaged to this actress. She plays Fiona Gallagher on Shameless, and has appeared in movies such as The Day After Tomorrow, The Phantom of the Opera, and Mystic River.", "Sam Esmail wrote and directed this 2014 film, which stars Emmy Rossum and Justin Long as a couple whose six-year relationship is depicted at various points in time."], "subcategory": "Trash Movies", "category": "Trash"}, {"leadin": "On the last day of 1801, this object was re-discovered by Franz Xaver von Zach using a method to calculate its orbit developed by Carl Gauss. For 10 points each:", "answers_sanitized": ["Ceres [SEER-eez]", "asteroids", "Dawn"], "parts": ["Name this object initially discovered by Giuseppe Piazza on the first day of 1801.", "The dwarf planet Ceres is located in between Mars and Jupiter in a belt named for these objects, very few of which are found in the Kirkwood gaps.", "This spacecraft, launched in 2007, explored Vesta in 2011, and is currently exploring Ceres."], "subcategory": "Science Other", "category": "Science"}, {"leadin": "This policy began in 1948 and has a name meaning \u201cseparateness.\u201d For 10 point each:", "answers_sanitized": ["Apartheid", "Robben Island", "African National Congress"], "parts": ["Name this policy of racial segregation in South Africa.", "During apartheid, this island held prisoners such as the poet Dennis Brutus and Nelson Mandela.", "Mandela was a co-founder of the Spear of the Nation, the armed faction of this larger political party which was removed from the US Terror Group list in 2008."], "subcategory": "History World", "category": "History"}, {"leadin": "This author fictionalized the story of a German adventurer with an iron prosthetic hand in Gotz von Berlichingen. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Johan Wolfgang von Goethe [GUR-tuh]", "The Sorrows of Young Werther", "epistolary novel"], "parts": ["What author better known for a version of the Faust story also wrote a novel in which the title character kills himself because he can\u2019t have Lotte?", "The Goethe novel mentioned above, in which the title character is buried under a Linden tree after his suicide, is titled what?", "Werther is told to the reader through a series of letters, a literary form known by this name."], "subcategory": "Literature European", "category": "Literature"}, {"leadin": "In the dialogue Theaetetus, Socrates relates the apocryphal tale that this philosopher fell in a well while looking at the stars. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Thales", "water", "solar eclipse"], "parts": ["What founder of the Milesian school averred the pantheistic view that \u201ceverything is full of gods.\u201d", "Thales thought this was the primary substance from which all other things come. Empedocles grouped this essential substance with earth, air, and fire.", "Herodotus said Thales predicted one of these events which occurred during a battle between the Medes and the Lydians."], "subcategory": "Philosophy Classical", "category": "Philosophy"}, {"leadin": "This man was awarded the former seat of John Breckenridge by the Kentucky legislature. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["Henry Clay", "The American System", "William Jones and/or Langdon Cheves and/or Nicholas Biddle"], "parts": ["Name this member of the senate\u2019s Great Triumvirate, along with John Calhoun and Daniel Webster, whose nickname was the Great Compromiser.", "This economic plan attributed to Clay included individual concepts such as the preservation of the Bank of the United States and increased spending on internal improvements, such as canals and turnpikes.", "[5 each] Three different men served as President of the Second Bank of the United States. Name any two for five points each."], "subcategory": "History American", "category": "History"}, {"leadin": "This infinite viewpoint is seen by a story\u2019s narrator under the staircase of the mediocre poet Carlos Daneri. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["\u201cThe Aleph\u201d", "Jorge Luis Borges", "\u201cThe Library of Babel\u201d"], "parts": ["What letter of the Hebrew alphabet names the title point in which the narrator can see everything in the universe from all possible vantage points simultaneously?", "\u201cThe Aleph\u201d is a short story by this Argentine author fascinated by infinities, also the author of \u201cThe Garden of Forking Paths\u201d and the collection Ficciones.", "The narrator of this Borges story inhabits a series of interlocking hexagonal buildings including every book ever written and variants of every book ever written that are off by one letter, etcetera."], "subcategory": "Literature World", "category": "Literature"}, {"leadin": "Reye's syndrome has been linked to this drug, which can prevent a heart attack. FTPE:", "answers_sanitized": ["aspirin [or acetylsalicylic acid; or ASA]", "Bayer", "prostaglandins"], "parts": ["Name this nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drug commonly used to reduce fevers and relieve pain.", "Felix Hoffmann, a chemist for this German pharmaceutical company, synthesized aspirin.", "Aspirin blocks the production of thromboxanes and these compounds from arachidonic acid by inhibiting the enzyme cyclooxygenase. They were discovered in semen by Ulf von Euler."], "subcategory": "Science Chemistry", "category": "Science"}]}